<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>3dv - Tag - Andrea Conti PhD</title>
        <link>https://andreaconti.github.io/tags/3dv/</link>
        <description>3dv - Tag - Andrea Conti PhD</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>andrea.conti@tutanota.com (Andrea Conti)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>andrea.conti@tutanota.com (Andrea Conti)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:32:00 &#43;0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andreaconti.github.io/tags/3dv/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Range-Agnostic Multi-View Depth Estimation With Keyframe Selection</title>
    <link>https://andreaconti.github.io/projects/range_agnostic_multi_view_depth/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:32:00 &#43;0200</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://andreaconti.github.io/projects/range_agnostic_multi_view_depth/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Andrea Conti &middot Matteo Poggi &middot Valerio Cambareri &middot Stefano Mattoccia [Paper] [Code] [Demo] Overview Multi-View 3D reconstruction techniques process a set of source views and a reference view to yield an estimated depth map for the latter. Unluckily, state-of-the-art frameworks
require to know a priori the depth range of the scene, in order to sample a set of depth hypotheses and build a meaningful cost volume. do not take into account the keyframes selection.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Revisiting Depth Completion from a Stereo Matching Perspective for Cross-Domain Generalization</title>
    <link>https://andreaconti.github.io/projects/revisiting_depth_completion_from_stereo_matching/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:32:00 &#43;0200</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://andreaconti.github.io/projects/revisiting_depth_completion_from_stereo_matching/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a new framework for depth completion robust against domain-shifting issues. It exploits the generalization capability of modern stereo networks to face depth completion, by processing fictitious stereo pairs obtained through a virtual pattern projection paradigm. Any stereo network or traditional stereo matcher can be seamlessly plugged into our framework, allowing for the deployment of a virtual stereo setup that is future-proof against advancement in the stereo field. Exhaustive experiments on cross-domain generalization support our claims. Hence, we argue that our framework can help depth completion to reach new deployment scenarios]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
